so one of the things that i believe is going to really kind of break people's minds in these times
is that we talk a lot about community and um what that means is getting into more intimate
interactions with people that are not transactions and so that requires actually looking at scenarios
individually and what happens in the capitalism that we're really deep in is that it's kind of like
widgets are created there's just these very systematic protocols by which people operate
that ignore the uniqueness of different scenarios and situations and in doing so it causes a lot of
actual actual positive things to fall through the cracks but in community you really can't operate
that way because you're dealing with folks in a much more close interaction and so you have to see
them for their in unique selves their unique situations etc don't get me wrong i mean it's not
an easy thing but it's a necessary thing that actually sees the human you see that's the thing
that capitalism does so well it prevents us from seeing each other we start only seeing each other
as business and so we do this thing where we say don't take it personal it's just business and it's
like well it is personal because it's a person and business is an action and so what i think a lot of us
are having to like undo is that practicum and actually apply the praxis of looking at every scenario
individually which takes a lot more energy and time it takes nuance takes critical thinking etc but it
also allows us to get out of the matrix of transactionalism that does not see people that
does not see humanity beyond a dollar value sister seals this is your ancestor harriet tubman
you